Wyler, Julius; Papers ger102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wyler, 1916-1959; 3; 73 file folders
  - Papers prepared under the auspices of the Council of Research of the Institute of World Affairs of the New School for Social Research, by Julius Wyler and others, 1944-1951; 3.2
    - "Proposal for a Research Project on Industrialization and the Pattern of World Trade", 1944 December 9; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 18)
    - "Preliminary Report on the Research Project on Industrialization and the Pattern of World Trade", Undated; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 19)
    - "First Progress Report of the Research Project on Industrialization and the Pattern of World Trade", 1947 May 17; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 20)
    - Sumberg, Theodore A. "Strategic Factors of Industrialization", 1946-1947; typescripts (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 21)
    - Wyler, Julius. "Notes on the Research Project on Industrialization", 1947 September; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 22)
    - Wyler, Julius. "Considerations on the Research Project on the Process of Industrialization", Undated; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 23)
    - Aubrey, Henry G. "Remarks to the drafts of Dr. Wyler and Mr. Somberg", 1947 October; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 24)
    - Schatz, Sayre P. Untitled notes on the industrialization project, Undated; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 25)
    - The Institute of World Affairs, NSSR. "Proposal for Two Research Projects in the Field of Economic Development", 1949 March; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 26)
    - The Institute of World Affairs, NSSR. "Financing World Economic Development. A Survey of Research Problems", 1949 June; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 27)
    - The Institute of World Affairs, NSSR (Aubrey). "A New Outline of Development Problems", 1950 October 18; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 28)
    - "Industrialization and Foreign Trade -- Germany", Undated; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 29)
    - "Industrialization and Foreign Trade -- United Kingdom", Undated; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 30)
    - Wyler, Julius. "The Dynamics of American Industrialization", Undated; typescript, mimeographed (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 31)
    - Wyler, Julius. "The Dynamics of American Industrialization", Undated; typescript, early versions (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 32)
    - Wyler, Julius. "The Industrial Development of the United States", 1949 Spring; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 33)
    - Aubrey, Henry G. "The Place of Small Industry in Economic Development. Research Project on Financing World Economic Development", 1951 May; typescript (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 34)
  - Course outlines, reading lists, handouts, etc. for courses taught by Wyler at the New School for Social Research, Undated; 3.3
    - Applied Statistics / Elementary Statistics, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 35)
    - Elementary Statistics -- bibliographies, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 36)
    - General Statistics (I), Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 37)
    - Industrial Development of the United States -- outlines, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 38)
    - Industrial Development of the United States -- tables, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 39)
    - Introduction to Economic Research -- bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 40)
    - National Income and National Wealth, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 41)
    - Sources and Methods of Statistical Estimates, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 42)
    - Statistical Analysis of National Income and War Finance, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 43)
    - The Structure of the World Economy, Undated (Box 2 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by Julius V. Wy), Folder 44)
- Publications by Others, Undated; 4; 66 file folders
  This series contains primarily reprints by colleagues and other scholars, which were sent to Wyler.
  - Amonn, Alfred, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 1)
  - Arrow, Kenneth J., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 2)
  - Aubrey, Henry G., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 3)
  - Barnes, Leo, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 4)
  - Bauer, Walter, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 5)
  - Balassa, Bela A., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 6)
  - Benham, Frederic, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 7)
  - Biske, Käthe, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 8)
  - Bjerve, Petter Jakob, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 9)
  - Böhler, Eugen, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 10)
  - Brecht, Arnold, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 11)
  - Brown, H. P., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 12)
  - Burkhead, Jesse, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 13)
  - Cohn, Edmond N., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 14)
  - Copeland, M. A., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 15)
  - Dandekar, V. M., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 16)
  - Derksen, J. B. D., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 17)
  - Eynern, Gert von, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 18)
  - Fellner, Fréderic de, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 19)
  - Frankel, S. Herbert, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 20)
  - Ghosh, A., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 21)
  - Gini, Corrado, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 22)
  - Grunebaum, L. H., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 23)
  - Gumbel, Emil J., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 24)
  - Haavelmo, Trygve, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 25)
  - Hitschmann, Emil, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 26)
  - Horowitz, C. Morris. "Methods in Principles of Statistical Analysis", Undated; mimeographed typescript (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 27)
  - Horvath, Barna, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 28)
  - Jasny, Naum, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 29)
  - Johnson, Alvin, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 30)
  - Kallen, Horace M., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 31)
  - Kapp, K. William, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 32)
  - Kaufmann, Felix, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 33)
  - Kaufmann, George, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 34)
  - Keller, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 35)
  - Krakauer, Siegfried, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 36)
  - Kull, Walter, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 37)
  - Kullmann, Eugen, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 38)
  - Landmann, Michael, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 39)
  - Littmann, Konrad, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 40)
  - Livi, Livio, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 41)
  - Lowe, Adolph, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 42)
  - Mayer, Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 43)
  - Meyer, Julie, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 44)
  - Mombert, François, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 45)
  - Moore, Wilbert E., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 46)
  - Neisser, Hans, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 47)
  - Neumark, Fritz, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 48)
  - Predöhl, Andreas, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 49)
  - Redding, A. David, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 50)
  - Sauvy, A., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 51)
  - Schutz, Alfred, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 52)
  - Shirras, G. Findlay, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 53)
  - Shoup, Carl S., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 54)
  - Singh, Baljit, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 55)
  - Strauss, Ludwig, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 56)
  - Szmak, G. C., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 57)
  - Tintner, Gerhard, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 58)
  - Welter, Erich, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 59)
  - Williams, K., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 60)
  - Winkler, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 61)
  - Wood, Marshall K., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 62)
  - Wunderlich, Frieda, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 63)
  - Yardi, M. R., Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 64)
  - Zurukzoglu, St, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 65)
  - Zwingli, Ulrich, Undated (Box 3 (4-Publications by Others), Folder 66)
- Pamphlets, 1903-1967; 5; 37 file folders
  This series contains pamphlets, primarily on topics in economics.
  - Fünfzig Jahre Institut für Weltwirtschaft an der Universität Kiel, 1964 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - Graduate Training in Economics. A Report on Panel Discussions at Yale, 1956 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 68)
  - The International Finance Corporation, 1956 August 10 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 69)
  - Das Kommunistische Manifest. Mit Vorreden von Karl Marx und Friedrich Engels, 1919 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 70)
  - Political Economy in the Soviet Union, 1944 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 71)
  - Bilkur, Sefik.National Economy of Turkey, 1949 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 72)
  - Böhler, Eugen.Technik und Wirtschaft in den geistigen Entscheidungen der Gegenwart, 1931 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 73)
  - Burns, Arthur F.Stepping Stones Towards the Future. Twenty-Seventh Annual Report of the National Bureau of Economic Research, 1947 March (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 74)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics.Report for 1947 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 75)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics.Report for Period January 1, 1948-June 30, 1949 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 76)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics.Report for Period July 1, 1949-June 30, 1950 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 77)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics.Rational Decision-Making and Economic Behavior. 19th Annual Report July 1, 1950-June 30, 1951 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 78)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics.Report for Period July 1, 1952-June 30, 1954, 1955 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 79)
  - Erdmann, Karl Dietrich.Wissenschaft im Dritten Reich, 1967 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 80)
  - Guggenheim-Grünberg, Florence.Pfarrer Ulrich als Missionar im Surbtal, 1953 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 81)
  - Head, J. G.The Welfare Foundations of Public Finance Theory, 1965 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 82)
  - Herbertz, Richard.Philosophie und Einzelwissenschaften, 1913 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 83)
  - IFO-Institut für Wirtschaftsforschung (München).Das Konjunturtest-Verfahren und seine wirtschaftswissenschaftliche Bedeutung, 1951 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 84)
  - International Association for Research into Income and Wealth.By-Laws. List of Members, 1953 October (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 85)
  - King, Gregory.Two Tracts, 1936 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 86)
  - Knight, Frank H.Economic Freedom and Social Responsibility, 1952 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 87)
  - League of Nations.Quantitative Trade Controls. Their Causes and Nature, 1943 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 88)
  - Mayer, Kurt B.Economic Development and Population Growth in Rhode Island, 1953 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 89)
  - McBride, Katherine.The Central Conflict in Present-Day Education: Its Psychological References, 1948 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 90)
  - National Planning Association.Modernizing the American Economy, 1964 December (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 91)
  - National Tax Association.Preliminary Report of the Committee of the National Tax Association on Federal Taxation of Corporations, 1938 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 92)
  - Patinkin, Don.Relative Prices, Say's Law and the Demand for Money, and The Indeterminacy of Absolute Prices in Classical Economic Theory, 1949 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 93)
  - Plenge, Johann.Das System der Verkehrswirtschaft, 1903 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 94)
  - Rist, Leonard.The European Common Market. Address by Leonard Rist, Economic Director of the World Bank to the Annual Meeting of the International Advertising Association, Inc. New York, 1958 May 16 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - Steiger, A.Spittelers Sprachkunst. Zu Carl Spittelers 70. Geburtstage 24. April 1915 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce.American Direct Investments in Foreign Countries -- 1936, 1938 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce (Amos E. Taylor).The Balance of International Payments of the United States in 1935, 1936 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 98)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce.Foreign Investments in the United States, 1937 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 99)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce.Oversea Travel and Travel Expenditures in the Balance of International Payments of the United States 1919-38, 1939 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 100)
  - Wallace, H. A.Industrial Prices and Their Relative Flexibility, 1935 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 101)
  - Werminghoff, Albert.Unsere Volkszahl in Vergangenheit und Gegenwart, 1917 (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 102)
  - Woytinsky, Emma S.Bibliography of the Writings of W. S. Woytinsky, 1961 May (Box 3 (5-Pamphlets), Folder 103)
- Course and research notes and materials, Undated; 6; 91 file folders
  This series consists of folders, primarily of handwritten notes on various topics, both for courses taught by Wyler as well as topics of research for his publications. Included in this series are several full-length versions, primarily handwritten, of textbooks for courses taught by Wyler.
  - Jasny, Naum. "On the Wrong Track", 1956; typescript (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 1)
  - Tagliacrozzo, Giorgio. "Croce and Economic Liberalism", 1950; mimeographed typescript (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 2)
  - Applied Statistics, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 3)
    Handwritten and typewritten text.
  - Applied Statistics -- History of Statistics, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 4)
  - Applied Statistics -- Labor, Manufacturing, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 5)
  - Applied Statistics -- Materials, Population, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 6)
  - Applied Statistics -- Questionnaire, Tables, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 7)
  - Elementary General Statistics, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 8)
    Typewritten and handwritten text.
  - Elementary Statistics -- notes, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 9)
  - Elementary Statistics -- Handouts, Tables, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 10)
  - Sources and Methods of Statistical Estimates, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 11)
  - Statistics -- Calculations, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 12)
  - Statistics -- I. Significance and Use. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 13)
  - Statistics -- II. Enumeration and Presentation. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 14)
  - Statistics -- III. Frequency Distribution and Averages, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 15)
  - Statistics -- IV. Variability, Skewness and Kurtosis, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 16)
  - Statistics -- V. Rates and Ratios. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 17)
  - Statistics -- VI. Index Numbers of Prices and Production. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 18)
  - Statistics -- VII. Correlation Simple and Linear. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 19)
  - Statistics -- VII. Correlation, Appendix. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 20)
  - Statistics -- VIII. Normal Frequency Distribution. Handwritten text, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 21)
  - Statistics, Mathematical, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 22)
  - Baby Boom -- Excerpts 1: International, general, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 23)
  - Baby Boom -- Excerpts 2: National, Undated (Box 4 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 24)
  - Baby Boom -- International Statistics, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 1)
  - Baby Boom -- Australia, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 2)
  - Baby Boom -- France, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 3)
  - Baby Boom -- Germany, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 4)
  - Baby Boom -- Great Britain: Ireland, England, Wales, Scotland, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 5)
  - Baby Boom -- Netherlands, Belgium, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 6)
  - Baby Boom -- Scandinavia: Sweden, Norway, Denmark, Finland, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 7)
  - Baby Boom -- United States, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 8)
  - Balance of Payments (1) -- Switzerland, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 9)
  - Balance of Payments (2) -- International Capital Movements Project, Geneva, 1939 (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 10)
  - Balance of Payments (3) -- Canada, US, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 11)
  - Balance of Payments (3) -- Australia, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 12)
  - Economic Research -- Seminar notes, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 13)
  - History -- Medieval Europe, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 14)
  - Industrialization -- Capital, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 15)
  - Industrialization -- Censuses, 1840-1870 (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 16)
  - Industrialization, 1840-1880 (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 17)
  - Industrialization -- Census figures, 1849-1899 (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 18)
  - Industrialization -- Growth studies, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 19)
  - Industrialization -- Hoffmann, Schlote, Zweig, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 20)
  - Industrialization -- Machinery, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 21)
  - Industrialization -- Output, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 22)
  - Industrialization -- Productivity, Undated (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 23)
  - Industrialization -- Texts, 1840-1937 (Box 5 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 24)
  - Industrialization -- UK machinery, trade, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 1)
  - Industrialization -- UK and Germany, comparisons, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 2)
  - Industrialization -- World trade statistics, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 3)
  - Industrialization -- Old texts, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 4)
  - Industrial Development -- Agriculture, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 5)
  - Industrial Development -- Automobiles, Petroleum, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 6)
  - Industrial Development -- Building Materials, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 7)
  - Industrial Development -- Colonial Times, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 8)
  - Industrial Development -- Comparisons, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 9)
  - Industrial Development -- Food, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 10)
  - Industrial Development -- Horsepower, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 11)
  - Industrial Development -- Iron and Steel, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 12)
  - Industrial Development -- Periods, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 13)
  - Industrial Development -- Regional, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 14)
  - Industrial Development -- Shoes, Clothing, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 15)
  - Industrial Development -- Textiles, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 16)
  - Industrial Development -- Textiles, Europe, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 17)
  - Industrial Development -- Technical, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 18)
  - Industrial Development -- United Kingdom, Machinery and Trade, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 19)
  - International Association for Research in Income and Wealth, 1947-1951 (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 20)
  - International Trade, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 21)
  - The Linguistic Character of East Prussia -- Notes, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 22)
  - The Linguistic Character of East Prussia -- text, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 23)
  - National Income -- course notes, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 24)
  - National Income in Constant Prices, Undated (Box 6 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 25)
  - National Income, Undated (Box 7 (6-Course and research notes and materials), Folder 1)
    Typewritten text.